http://www.red-c.co.uk/privacy-policy

020 3397 9028ServicesServices overviewConsultancy and strategyMobile app developmentWebsite developmentUX/UI designEnterprise mobile solutionsHosting and maintenanceWeb Service and APIsSecurity AssessmentAugmented realityDigital scorecardCase studiesSectorsSectors overviewFinancialHealthcareUtilitiesNon-profitConsumerAboutBlogContact0203 397 9028ServicesServices overviewConsultancy and strategyMobile app developmentWebsite developmentUX/UI designEnterprise mobile solutionsHosting and maintenanceWeb Service and APIsAugmented realityCase studiesSectorsSectors overviewFinancialHealthcareUtilitiesNon-profitConsumerStartupsAboutBlogContactPrivacy PolicyRed C Mobile Ltd operates http://www.red-c.co.uk (the "Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.1.0 OUR CORE BELIEFS REGARDING USER PRIVACY AND DATA PROTECTION• User privacy and data protection are human rights• We have a duty of care to the people within our data• Data is a liability, it should only be collected and processed when absolutely necessary• We will never sell, rent or otherwise distribute or make public your personal information2.0 RELEVANT LEGISLATIONAlong with our business and internal computer systems, this website is designed to comply with the following national and international legislation with regards to data protection and user privacy:• UK Data Protection Act 1988 (DPA)• EU Data Protection Directive 1995 (DPD)• EU General Data Protection Regulation 2018 (GDPR)This site’s compliance with the above legislation, all of which are stringent in nature, means that this site is likely compliant with the data protection and user privacy legislation set out by many other countries and territories as well. If you are unsure about whether this site is compliant with your own country of residences’ specific data protection and user privacy legislation you should contact our data protection officer (details of whom can be found in section 9.0) for clarification.3.0 PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT THIS WEBSITE COLLECTS AND WHY WE COLLECT ITThis website collects and uses personal information for the following reasons:3.1 Site visitation trackingLike most websites, this site uses Google Analytics (GA) to track user interaction. We use this data to determine the number of people using our site, to better understand how they find and use our web pages and to see their journey through the website.Although GA records data such as your geographical location, device, internet browser and operating system, none of this information personally identifies you to us. GA also records your computer’s IP address which could be used to personally identify you but Google do not grant us access to this. We consider Google to be a third party data processor (see section 6.0 below).GA makes use of cookies, details of which can be found on Google’s developer guides. FYI our website uses the analytics.js implementation of GA.Disabling cookies on your internet browser will stop GA from tracking any part of your visit to pages within this website.In addition to Google Analytics, this website may collect information (already held in the public domain) attributed to the IP address of the computer or device that is being used to access it.3.2 Our WebsiteShould you choose to download any of the material on the Red C website, we will request from your first name, last name and email address. Should you choose not to share this information, we will not collect any information other google analytics tracking (which you can read more about in section 3.1 Site visitation tracking.If you are under 16 years of age you MUST obtain parental consent before supplying any personal information on the Red C website.3.3 Contact forms and email linksShould you choose to contact us using the contact form on our Contact us page, none of the data that you supply will be stored by this website, instead the data will be automatically entered into Hubspot, our marketing and sales system.3.4 Email newsletterIf you choose to join our email newsletter, the email address that you submit to us will be forwarded to MailChimp and stored in Hubspot who provide us with email, marketing and sales services. We consider MailChimp and Hubspot to be a third party data processor (see section 6.0 below). The email address that you submit will not be stored within this website’s own database or in any of our internal computer systems.Your email address will remain within MailChimp and Hubspot database for as long as we continue to use MailChimp and Hubspot services for email, marketing and sales services or until you specifically request removal from the list. You can do this by unsubscribing using the unsubscribe links contained in any email newsletters that we send you or by clicking ‘Unsubscribe’ at the bottom of the newsletter, otherwise you can contact us here. When requesting removal via our contact us page, please send your email to us using the email account that is subscribed to the mailing list.If you are under 16 years of age you MUST obtain parental consent before joining our email newsletter.While your email address remains within the MailChimp and Hubspot database, you will receive periodic (approximately one per month) newsletter-style emails from us.4.0 HOW WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONAs detailed in section 3.2 above, if you submit a your information to the Red C website via any post published on this website no personal information will be stored within this website’s database, however, will be automatically entered into Hubspot, our marketing and sales system. This is currently the only occasion where personal data will be stored via by Red C via our website.5.0 ABOUT THIS WEBSITE'S SERVERThis website is hosted by Webflow within and information about hosting can be found here.Some of the data centre’s more notable security features are as follows:• Protection against distributed denial of service (DDoS) attacks• Webflow provides SSL certificates for all sites hosted in WebflowFull details of Webflow’s data centre can be found here.All traffic (transferral of files) between this website and your browser is encrypted and delivered over HTTPS.6.0 OUR THIRD PARTY DATA PROCESSORSWe use a number of third parties to process personal data on our behalf. These third parties have been carefully chosen and all of them comply with the legislation set out in section 2.0. These third parties are based in the UK and USA and the links through to their privacy policies are available below:• Google (Privacy policy)• Mailchimp (Privacy policy)• Hubspot (Privacy policy)• Tawk.to (Privacy policy)• Webflow (Privacy policy)7.0 SECURITY AND DATA BREACHESThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. Should there be any breach of your personal data, we will inform you within 72 hours of knowing of it. We strive to ensure your personal information is protected at all times.8.0 DATA CONTROLLERThe data controller of this website is: Red C Mobile Limited, a UK Private limited Company with company number: 03476303Whose registered office is:4th Floor 74 Great Eastern Street, London, EC2A 3JL9.0 DATA PROTECTION OFFICERMiss Rikki LevittProject ManagerTelephone: 020 3397 9129Email: rikki.levitt@red-c.co.uk10.0 CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICYThis privacy policy may change from time to time in-line with legislation or industry developments. We will not explicitly inform our clients or website users of these changes. Instead, we recommend that you check this page occasionally for any policy changes. Specific policy changes and updates are mentioned in the changelog below.10.1 Change log• 22/05/2018• Updated to the Red C privacy policy detailing Red C’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) policy and our commitment to our clients and . website visitors data.Let’s speak!Provide us with your contact details and we will contact you shortly.I agree to our Terms and ConditionsThank you! Your submission has been received!Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.020 3397 9028info@red-c.co.ukServicesCase studiesSectorsABOUTBlogCONTACT
COO, Centtrip LimitedThe app function as expected, satisfying its users and the client and leading to more work for Red C London. The team produces high-quality development work on time and at reasonable prices. Their collaborative nature and valuable suggestions make for an effective workflow.© 2019 Red C Mobile Limited Registered in England and Wales. Registration No 03476303 All rights reserved.Privacy Policy
